要是我們拍個自己的廣告呢
Well, what if we made our own commercial,
展示綠點最愛的海鮮餐廳里
showing all the-the sweet down-home faces
甜美簡樸的人
at Greenpoint's favorite seafood restaurant,
菜單來源于露易絲的家族食譜
where the menu comes straight out of Louise's family recipes
和60年的傳統
and-and 60 years of tradition!
如果我們拍廣告  我們可以向那些企業混蛋展示
If we did a commercial, we could show those corporate butts
我們本地的南方魅力
our homegrown southern charm!
真是個好主意  珍妮
That's a great idea, Jenny.
拍廣告是個復雜的工作
Directing a commercial's a big job.
你需要一個對餐廳  食物
You need somebody who knows the restaurant, the food,
以及人民了如指掌的人
the people like the back of her hand.
但最重要的是你需要一個
But mostly you need someone
沒有穿著睡衣在城里閑逛的人
who's not wandering around town in her pajamas.
珍妮可以做到
Yeah, Jenny can do it!
什么  不不
What?! Oh, no, no.
我們應該雇用一個專業人士
We should definitely hire a professional for this.
綠點雇用不起專業人士
Greenpoint can't afford a professional.
嚴格來說我們現在甚至沒有警力
We technically don't even have a police force right now.
我們仰仗公民的逮捕
We rely on citizen's arrests.
-什么  -當我沒說
- Oh, what? - Never mind, forget I said that.
但是現在還有足夠的備用現金
But there is just enough money left in the till
支持你拍廣告
for you to make the commercial.
我不是賭徒  但我建議我們
I'm not a gambling man, but I say we put